<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nick Johnston</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Nick Johnston</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="api_base">http://104.214.69.148/nick_johnston_web_backend/api.php</string>
    <string name="api_table_news">news</string>
    <string name="api_table_video">youtube_videos</string>
    <string name="api_table_albums">album</string>
    <string name="api_table_music">music</string>
    <string name="api_table_concert">concerts</string>
    <string name="api_table_users">users</string>


    <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">AIzaSyATDSCcngHPKHomcL0ZVQz7_aMEzXp0f3A</string>


    <string name="menu_title_discography">Biography</string>
    <string name="menu_title_jamming">Videos</string>
    <string name="menu_title_news">News</string>
    <string name="menu_title_live_concert">Gigs</string>
    <string name="menu_title_music">Music</string>
    <string name="menu_title_music_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_title_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="menu_title_contact_us">Get in touch</string>

    <string name="about">
        "Hi! My name is Nick Johnston and I’m a Canadian musician! I love guitar, reading, cartoons, video games, comic books, eating delicious food and drinking as much coffee as any one human being can until they explode!
        I started playing guitar 14 years ago – which means I’ve been playing guitar  exactly half my life! I feel at 28 years old, I am still an infant with the instrument. There is always so much to learn and always so much to hear! I am a self-taught musician. Everything I have learned about music and it’s inner-workings has come from listening, experimenting and writing music.
        I had a neighbour who was 1 year older than me and I found out that he was a guitar player. At 13 years old, I idolized him and wanted to be as cool as he was! I would go over to his basement and watch him play for hours. I’ve never needed any motivation – I’ve always loved the instrument!
        I don’t think I ever had a practice routine. I would learn whichever songs were in the monthly guitar magazines (GuitarOne was my favourite!) or try and figure stuff out by ear. Once I gained a little facility on the instrument, I started getting into the realm of lead guitar. Metallica, Led Zeppelin, Ozzy Osbourne and Black Sabbath satisfied my hunger. I then got more into the ‘virtuoso’ world a bit – Yngwie, SRV, EVH, Jeff Beck, Satriani Etc.. After that, I started working on my own music.
        I think it’s important to learn as much as you possibly can! It’s essential to figure out what works for you as an individual when it comes to absorbing and applying new pieces of information that are presented.  I did not take guitar lessons or attend a music college, but that’s just because I know that for the type of musician I am, I wouldn’t have thrived. I like to figure stuff out at my own pace and learn through trial and error. At any rate, figure out what works for you and you’ll be just fine!"
    </string>


    <string name="error_player">There was an error initializing the YouTubePlayer (%1$s)</string>


    <string name="privacy_policy">Nick Johnston
</string>


    <string name="cd_play">Play and pause</string>
    <string name="cd_next">Skip forwards</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_news">ScrollingActivity_news</string>

</resources>
