<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nick Johnston</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Nick Johnston</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="api_base">http://104.214.69.148/band_app_backend/api.php</string>
    <string name="api_table_news">news</string>
    <string name="api_table_video">youtube_videos</string>
    <string name="api_table_albums">album</string>
    <string name="api_table_music">music</string>
    <string name="api_table_concert">concerts</string>
    <string name="api_table_users">users</string>


    <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">AIzaSyATDSCcngHPKHomcL0ZVQz7_aMEzXp0f3A</string>


    <string name="menu_title_discography">Biography</string>
    <string name="menu_title_jamming">Videos</string>
    <string name="menu_title_news">News</string>
    <string name="menu_title_live_concert">Gigs</string>
    <string name="menu_title_music">Music</string>
    <string name="menu_title_music_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_title_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="menu_title_contact_us">Get in touch</string>

    <string name="about">
        "Nemesis is a Bangladeshi rock band formed in 1999 by a group of school friends. After a few changes in the line-up during the initial years, the band started to gain ground within Dhaka's local music scene with their fluent performances, as it settled on to a permanent line-up with Zohad on vocals, Maher and Nondito on guitars, Ratul on bass and Yawar on drums. This earned them a spot in a 'mixed album' compilation tagged 'Agontuk-2' in 2003. Debuting with their first single 'Obocheton', Nemesis became an instant favorite among Dhaka's listeners which, in turn, led to a record deal with G-Series.

During the recording of the album, their drummer Yawar had to leave and was replaced by Dio who worked on the rest of the album and their guitarist Nondito left soon after to be replaced by Omayr in 2005. Nemesis’ debut album ‘Onneshon’ was finally released in 2005 under the label of G-Series, and it went on to become one of the major albums of that year. The album instantly stood out and generated a lot of attention with several of the songs proving to be major hits with the audience. With the release of 'Dhushor Bhabona' (2006) and 'Joyoddhoni' (2007), Nemesis earned mainstream recognition as both the singles went on to be included in the capital’s most popular FM station Radio Foorti’s Top 100 Singles Charts.

The band recorded their second album ‘Tritio Jatra’, six years later being released in 2011 under the label of Dead Line Music (DLM) sponsored by Cat’s Eye. The first single from the album ‘Kobe’ was released in Radio stations earlier in the 2011. In late 2011, they released the music video of their hit song ‘Kobe’ which was produced by Studio Bangi.
In 2012, Maher Khan and Omayr Khan left Nemesis and were later in the same year replaced by Zerif Ahmed and Zeheen Ahmed. In early 2013, Zeheen took a break from the band and was replaced by Zafir which is the present permanent line up of the band.

‘Tritio Jatra’ got nominated for The Best Band Award of 2011 (Popular Choice and Critic), The Best Sounding Album Award and Best Music Video Award (‘Kobe’, Studio Bangi) for the Citycell Channel I Music Awards where Nemesis won The Critic’s Choice - Best Band Award.

During the years, Nemesis had been engaged in numerous concerts and events largely concerning social awareness issues amongst other relevant affairs. Of these, the events well worth a mention are: ‘Say No To Drugs’ concert in Gulshan Youth Club (2008), ‘Save the Children’, ‘Stand up Against Poverty’ concerts in the Dhanmondi Amphitheater (2009), ‘Vote for Sundarban’ concert at the Army Stadium organized by BAMBA (2010) and the UNDP sponsored 'Say No to Violence Against Women' organized by BAMBA (2011 and 2012).

Along with live performances, Nemesis has also appeared in several different radio and television programs as well as media publications. The album has gone on to receive wide critical acclaim, and has seen the band establish themselves as forerunners to represent the next generation of rock in Bangladesh's proud musical history."
    </string>


    <string name="error_player">There was an error initializing the YouTubePlayer (%1$s)</string>


    <string name="privacy_policy">Nick Johnston
</string>


    <string name="cd_play">Play and pause</string>
    <string name="cd_next">Skip forwards</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_news">ScrollingActivity_news</string>

</resources>
